21ao1.info 2009-12-23

# Privacy Policy Statement

PRIVACY POLICY

21ao.com is dedicated to protect the home user’s privacy. This privacy statement explains our privacy practices for our site [ 21ao.com](http://21ao.com/). We feel it is important that visitors are fully knowledgeable about the use of their personal information.By using our website and/or purchasing our product, you expressly consent to the terms of this policy.

**Personal Information**

21ao.com allows you to visit the website without revealing any personal information about yourself. Your visit to this website is anonymous. We will only collect your contact information (first name, last name, billing address, phone number, email address and any other relevant information provided by you) as well as financial information (account or credit card numbers), with your permission and for the sole purpose of processing orders. 

If you make a purchase from our website, you will be asked to provide your name, billing address, email and credit card information (if you have chosen credit card as payment method). 21ao.com will use such information only for processing your order and to send important product specific information such as receipt, invoice or registration key.

The information you provide will not be used for any commercial purposes and will not be sold, rented, leased or otherwise forwarded to any third party. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you, and then only with partners who adhere to 21ao.com's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. 21ao.com may provide your personal information if necessary, in 21ao.com’s good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations of a governmental or regulatory body or in response to a valid subpoena, warrant, or order or to protect the rights of 21ao.com or others. 

Security Procedures and Credit Cards

In order to provide secure processing of your credit card when ordering, 21ao.com uses Secure Server Software (SSL) that is among the best in use today by e-commerce Web sites. Your personal information, including sensitive credit card information, is encrypted so that it is indecipherable by others as it travels across the Internet. No credit card data is stored in 21ao.com's Customer Database. All individual contact information provided to 21ao.com is stored in secure facilities. If at any time you would like to make a purchase, but do not want to provide your credit card information online, you may contact our Customer Support Staff for details on mail payment.

Cookies

Cookies are identifiers that a web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer in order to facilitate your next visit to the site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many web sites use them. 21ao.com does not use cookies that persist on your hard-drive. We do use dynamic, non-intrusive session cookies, which reside in your browser's memory only for the duration of your user session, to assist in the ordering and purchasing process. 21ao.com also uses data collected through session cookies for the purpose of identifying the source of traffic (which ad or link you used to reach us), and general patterns of activity on our site. No personally identifiable information is stored in this cookie. 21ao.com uses this data to better understand what services and support is valuable to our customers, and how we can continue to provide the best online experience possible to our users.

Links to Other Sites

Our site provides links to external web sites.21ao.com does not monitor or control the content of such web sites or whether such web sites collect or process your personal data. When you click on one of those links, you leave our site and enter one that we do not control and for which we cannot be responsible.21ao.com assumes no liability whatsoever for any kind of material available at such sites and recommends that you review their separate privacy policies.

Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using the web site or any services provided through the web site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. 21ao.com may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted to this site, so we encourage you to continuously review our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on this Website. Your continued use of 21ao.com or acceptance of our e-mails following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of these changes. 

Support 

21ao.com provides email support for users at our Helpdesk. 21ao.com does not currently provide telephone support. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our information handling practices, please contact us through the Helpdesk. We will do our best to respond to your inquiry within one business days.
